(忆往昔)
这具皮囊
This vessel...
用笼子的符文和咒语做了防护
...it's been warded with spellwork from the Cage.
你是我的
I own you.
我可能有凯莉·克莱恩的线索了
I think I have a lead on Kelly Kline.
她跟地狱王子大衮在一起
She's with Dagon, Prince of Hell,
在爱达荷州  科达伦
in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho.
艾琳·莱希
Eileen Leahy.
如果需要什么一定联系我  哪怕只想有人陪陪
Feel free to drop a line, even if you just wanna hang out.
我在肯德里克斯对狼人进行过深入研究
I did extensive research at Kendricks.
就像我们的
It's like our --
-霍格沃茨吗  -是啊
- Hogwarts? - ‭Exactly.
真好  找谁呢  混蛋捉鬼队
Great. Who you gonna call? Douchebusters.
厉害
Bravo.
我们现在跟他们合作了
We're working with these people now.
他们能力越强  我们也越好
The better they are, the better we are.
-你把她怎么了  -我有命在身
- What did you do to her? - I had orders.
你杀了她
So you killed her?
我们可以再给你个机会
We'll give you a second chance.
别搞砸了  不会再有一次了
Just don't mess it up. There won't be a third.
(如今)
(英国  伦敦城外)
你觉得她找我们什么事
What do you think she wants?
不会是好事
Nothing good.
(肯德里克斯学院)
你圣诞回家吗
Going home for Christmas?
抱歉  我忘了
Sorry. Forgot.
我会像以往一样待在这儿的
I'll be here, as always.
先生们
Gentlemen.
校长夫人
Headmistress.
跟我来
Come with me.
蒂莫西
Timothy,
米克尔
Michael,
你们都在肯德里克斯通过了诸多试炼
you have both conquered many trials here at Kendricks,
要么是靠天赋
either through natural talent
要么是靠勤奋
or good old-fashioned hard work.
但今天
But today,
今天  我们要看看你们中谁
today we'll learn which of you
能进入训练的下一阶段
matriculates to the next level of training.
本组织要承担重要的工作  先生们
This organization does important work, gentlemen --
我们的工作让数百万人
work which allows millions of people
晚上可以安然入睡
to sleep safely in their beds at night.
但要做这份工作
But in order to do this work,
要保护那些人
to protect those people,
我们需要学员能使用他们的技能
we need cadets who will employ their skills
能毫不质疑地执行命令
and execute orders without question.
因此
And so...
你们中只有一人能离开这间屋子
...only one of you will be leaving this room.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
他的抵抗很顽强
He -- he fought well.
他不想死的
He didn't want to die.
但准则另有要求
Yet the Code demands otherwise.
很好  戴维斯先生
Well played, Mr. Davies.
[邪恶力量 第12季第17集]
我们谈过之后
So, uh, after we talked,
-你又回爱达荷州科达伦了  -对
- you went back to Coeur d'Alene, Idaho? - ‭Right.
那是凯莉·克莱恩最后被见到的地方
The last place anybody saw Kelly Kline go --
我觉得该去看看
I figured I'd take a look.
怎样
And?
原来  她走之后
And turns out, right after she left,
有人烧了一间老仓库
somebody burned down an old warehouse.
我调查了一番
I did some digging.
看手机
Check your phone.
好
Okay.
那是什么  监控画面吗
What are those? Security shots?
没错  那是凯莉进去了
Oh, yeah. There's Kelly goin' in.
-干得好  艾琳  -谢谢
- Nice work, Eileen. - Thank you.
跟她在一起的女人是谁
So this chick with her,
佩特·班纳塔(歌手)模仿者吗
that, uh, Pat Benatar wannabe?
肯定是大衮了  嗯
It must be Dagon, I guess. Yeah.
太棒了  好吧  那...
Awesome. Okay, so --
那么
So...
凯莉和大衮去过这地方
Kelly and Dagon go crash this place,
然后那里就被烧了  巧合吗
and then it gets torched. Coincidence?
-不是  -绝对不是
- No. - Hell, no.
好吧  那是什么情况
All right, well, what are we lookin' at here?
还在查
Working on it.
去查到他们吧  艾琳
Well, go get 'em, Eileen.
就这么打算的
That's the plan.
再见  萨姆
Bye, Sam.
再见
Bye.
-好有爱  -得了
- That's cute. - ‭Come on.
我就是说  迪恩
Just saying, Dean,
就算有小卡和我们认识的每个猎人一起找
even with Cass and every Hunter we know working this,
我们还是几乎什么都查不到
we still got basically nothing.
至少  或许克劳力
At least, you know, maybe Crowley --
不行  我们不能找克劳力
No, dude, we're not calling Crowley -- ‭
小伙子们  来喝一杯吧
Hello, boys. Do come and have a drink.
你闯进了我们家吗
Did you break into our house?
我们的家  这是记录者的家
Our house. Men of Letters.
你们知道你们的钥匙
Did you know your key opens
能打开全世界的每个分部会所吗
every chapter house in the world?
你们说过会再给我个机会的
Well, you did say you'd give me a second chance.
那不代表我们想一起喝酒消遣
Yeah, that doesn't mean we wanna hang out.
你来有事吗
You here for a reason?
是的  还挺急的
I am, and it's a bit urgent.
一段时间之前  总部记录到了
Some time ago, the home office recorded
一段宇宙震波
some sort of cosmic shock wave.
很罕见
Very rare.
-几个月来...  -拿非利人
- And after a few months of -- - Nephilim.
你们知道
You knew?
是的
Yeah, we knew.
-怎么知道的  -说来话长
- How? - ‭Sort of a long story.
我有时间
Well, I've got time.
路西法附身了总统
Well, Lucifer jacked the President...
搞大了他女友的肚子
...and then knocked up his girlfriend.
现在  她在跟大衮逃命
And now, she is on the run with Dagon,
大衮是地狱王子
who is a Prince of Hell.
这样啊  你们没告诉我是因为
I see. And you didn't tell me this because...
因为这事算是个机密
'Cause it's kind of a need-to-know kind of thing.
魔鬼要有...
The Devil is having a...
孩子了
child.
这事似乎是我们需要知道的
It seems like something we'd need to know.
这女人现在在哪
Where is this woman now?
不确定
Not sure.
本来在我们手上
We had her.
我们想帮她的  但她...
Tried to help her, but, she, uh --
-她跑了  -嗯
- We lost her. - ‭Yeah.
抱歉  她本来在你们手上  你们却放过了她
I'm sorry. You -- you had her? And you let her live?
这不怪凯莉
Look, it's not Kelly's fault, okay?
她不知道她男友变成路西法了
She didn't know Lucifer was her boyfriend.
当然  这种事谁都可能碰上
Oh, sure, yeah. It could happen to anyone.
再说  她原本答应打胎的
Plus, she'd agreed to end the pregnancy.
我猜她后来改主意了
And I guess she changed her mind.
就算凯莉知道了前因后果
Even with everything Kelly knew, it...
那还是她的孩子  她做不到
it was still her kid. She couldn't.
那你们就该动手
Then you should have!
你们就该立刻一枪崩了她
You should've shot her between the eyes immediately.
怎么  因为换你就会那么做吗
Oh, why? 'Cause that's what you would've done?
就像你杀了那个狼人
Kind of like you killed that werewolf?
我记得  那让你受的惊可不小
'Cause from what I remember, that really messed you up.
嗯  因为你很看重第二次机会什么的
Yeah, 'cause you're so big on second chances and all.
是啊
Yeah -- yes.
我没说那会轻松
I'm not saying it was gonna be easy,
但这是准则的要求
but the Code demands it.
准则
"The Code."
这不是什么狼人
This is not some werewolf. Do --
你们知道如果这天谴之物
Do you have any idea what will happen
诞生了会怎么样吗
if this abomination is born?
米克
Mick...
我们在处理了  好吗  我们会找到她的
we're handling it, all right? We'll find her.
在那之前
So until then...
我们喝酒吧
I say we drink.
大衮
Dagon.
Dagon...
听到我
hear me.
我听到了  陛下
I do, sire.
说说我儿子
News of my son...
一切都好吗
All is well?
没什么意外
As can be expected.
那...容器呢
And the, uh...container?
她应该能撑到时候
She should last as long as needed.
那最好
Well, she better.
别让我失望  大衮
Don't fail me, Dagon.
别再辜负我了
Not again.
米克  外面没人
Mick, no one's out there.
如果我们逃跑  可能不会被抓
If we run, we might not get caught.
我们可以去找我父亲  他会...
We can go to my father. He'll --
关门  蒂莫西
Close the door, Timothy.
我们需要学员能毫不质疑地
We need cadets who will execute orders
执行命令
without question.
米克  我们得走了
Mick, we have to go.
你们中只有一人能离开这间屋子
Only one of you will be leaving this room.
米克
Mick.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
对不起
I'm...I'm sorry.
干什么
What?
你昨晚没报告情况  戴维斯先生
You didn't report in last night, Mr. Davies.
-有什么原因吗  -没有  夫人
- Is there a reason? - ‭No, ma'am.
我当时还在做调查
No, I was, uh, I was still in investigation mode.
-我本想通知您的  -那温家人呢
- I was gonna inform you. - And the Winchesters?
有些进展
Making some progress.
进来  罗林斯先生
Come in, Mr. Rawlings.
你知道贝维尔夫人认为他们无可救药吧
You are aware that Lady Bevell feels that they are hopeless.
是我收拾了她惹的祸
I'm the one cleaning up her mess.
海斯博士  据我所知
Dr. Hess, last I heard,
你和其他领导人
you and the rest of the leadership
认为拉拢温家人
felt getting the Winchesters
是拉拢美国猎人的关键
was key to bringing the American Hunters on board.
我只是在尽力实现
I'm just trying to make that happen.
是啊  情况有变
Yes, well, things change.
什么意思
And that means?
这个拿非利人
This... nephilim.
可怕的大麻烦
Something big and bad
就要来了  戴维斯先生
is on its way, Mr. Davies.
我们需要马上解决美国的情况
We need the situation in America settled now.
什么  我不懂
What? I don't understand.
那我说清楚点吧
Then let me make it blisteringly simple.
我们没时间
We don't have time
迎合几个肮脏的殖民地人了
to court a handful of mangy Colonials.
现在不行了
Not anymore.
所以萨姆和迪恩还有其他他们那群浑人
So either Sam and Dean and the rest of their ill-bred lot
要么学会服从
learn to obey,
要么你把他们交给凯奇先生
or you turn them over to Mr. Ketch...
然后重新开始
...and start fresh.
听着  我不认为
Look, I don't think --
这不是讨论
This is not a discussion.
是命令
It's an order.
听到了吗  米克尔
Are you hearing me, Michael?
要么同化
Assimilate or
要么消灭
eliminate.
你需要个枕头什么的吗
Do you need a pillow or...whatever?
怎么了
What's wrong?
我总感到一些奇怪的疼痛
I keep getting these weird little pains.
我相信你没事的
I'm sure everything's fine.
怎么  因为你怀孕的时候
Why? Because this is how you felt
也感觉到这样的疼了
all the times you were pregnant?
我需要见医生
I need to see a doctor.
医生是不会理解这孩子的  你都不怎么理解
No doctor will understand this child. You barely do.
我们在这里待太久了  该移动了
We've been here too long. We should go.
不
No!
你说会帮我的  我想看医生
You said that you would help me. I wanna see a doctor.
我确保宝宝没事之前哪里都不会去的
I'm not going anywhere until I know my baby's safe.
你气色好差
You look like crap.
你气色更差
Yeah, you look crappier.
真佩服米克
I gotta hand it to Mick.
你开个头  他能喝下太平洋
Man, you get him started, that guy can drink.
我们就很能喝了
I mean, we can drink,
但他简直是"能喝"金牌得主
but he's got, like, the "Can Drink" gold medal.
你最近跟妈妈通过话吗
Hey, you talk to Mom lately?
别担心你们妈妈
Oh, shouldn't worry about your Mum.
她和凯奇是很棒的组合
Her and Ketch make quite the team.
你会希望你妈跟他合作吗
Would you want your mom working with him?
说不好
Well, I can't say.
我根本不认识我妈妈
I never really knew my mum.
或是我爸
Or my dad.
我原本流落街头  直到被记录者发现
I was on the streets till the Men of Letters found me.
他们怎么发现你的
How did they find you?
我偷了一个记录者的钱包
I, uh, picked a member's pocket.
不是有意的  我就是想偷个几镑
Not on purpose. I was just after a couple of quid.
结果偷到了古巴比伦被诅咒的钱币
But I got a cursed coin from Ancient Babylon instead.
当然  这种事谁都能碰上
Yeah, sure. That could happen to anyone.
记录者认为我挺有前途
The Men of Letters decided I showed promised
就让我加入了
and signed me up.
他们给了我一份生活
They gave me a life.
他们...
They, um...
你没事吧
You all right?
嗯  当然
Yeah. Always.
有伏特加吗
Got any vodka?
你们好
Hello.
你就是凯莉吧
You must be Kelly.
你是她的...伴侣吗
And you're her...partner?
不是
No.
生育指导
Birth coach.
是啊
Sure.
凯莉的体征和初步检测都很好
Well, Kelly's vitals and preliminary labs were great.
我们就做个B超
So we're just gonna do a quick sonogram.
真有这必要吗
Is that really necessary?
当然了
Of course it is.
我们希望孩子住得开心
Want the baby to be a happy camper.
来这边
Right over here.
好了  凯莉
Okay, Kelly.
把单子掀起来  谢谢
Just lift up there, please. Thank you.
我要在镜头上涂点凝胶
I'm gonna put a little bit of gel on the camera,
所以会有点凉凉的
so it might be a little bit cold.
好了
Okay.
说"茄子"
Say "Cheese."
茄子
Cheese.
好吧
Okay.
看上去很好
It's looking good.
怎么了
What?
一切看上去都没问题
Everything looks a-okay.
Everything looks a-okay!
瞧  凯莉
See, Kelly?
你的宝宝是个小天使  就像我说的那样
Your baby is a little angel, just like I've been saying.
我知道这会有点尴尬
Now I know this can be a little bit awkward,
但为了给小家伙建立病例
but for the little champ's medical record,
能跟我说说孩子的父亲吗
what can you tell me about his father?
伟人竟堕落至此啊
How the mighty have sunk, eh?
乖狗狗
Good puppy.
狗狗想玩吗
Puppy want to play?
怎么了
What's the matter?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在给你你想要的  屈服
I'm giving you what you want -- submission.
-为什么  -为什么不呢
- Why? - Why not?
我明白了这里的规矩
I figured out the rules of the house,
考虑到一切
and...well, all things considered,
我宁可待在这里  而不是在笼子里发霉
I think I'd rather be here than rotting in the Cage
跟我流着口水  疯疯癫癫而且并不好玩的
with my drooling, insane -- and not in a fun way --
弟弟米迦勒待在一起
little bro Michael.
真的
Really?
Yes.
这是你的游戏
It's your game,
你的规则
your rules, so, uh...
所以  我可以配合
I figure I can work with that.
你赢了
You win.
现在做什么
What now...
陛下
sire?
-凯奇  -上报一下
- Ketch. - ‭Quick update --
那些流浪汉原来是易形者
the skels turned out to be shape-shifters.
-杀了一群七个人  -是八个
- Killed a clan of seven. - ‭Eight.
她说是八个
Eight, she says.
我已经知道不该跟她争了
I've learned not to argue.
你能搞定文书工作吧
Um, you'll make with the typey typey, yes?
我会提交报告的
I'll file the report.
太棒了  再见
Splendid. Ciao.
你和米克
So you and Mick...
一直是朋友吗
longtime friends?
更像是幸存者吧
More...survivors than friends.
我们曾一起上学
We were in school together.
主修杀人  辅修搞破坏吗
Major in murder, minor in mayhem? ‭
嗯
Yeah.
听说你的训练更多是即兴发挥的
I gather your training was a bit more...improvisational?
我们边干边学
We learned on the job.
然后你  放弃了那种生活
And then you... gave it all up.
我想要平静的普通生活
I wanted a quiet, normal life.
但你不久前
And yet, there you were,
还杀了一堆易形者
up to your elbows in shifter guts.
温太太
‭Mrs. Winchester...
我认为你就喜欢危险
I believe you're drawn to danger.
干杯
Cheers.
抱歉打搅
Sorry to interrupt.
没那个必要  戴维斯先生
There's really no need for that, Mr. Davies.
我们认识吗
We know each other?
我是兰尼·罗林斯
I'm Renny. Rawlings.
我从肯德里克斯毕业后
I've been working directly for Dr. Hess
一直在海斯博士手下工作
since I graduated Kendricks.
我是班级状元
Top of my class.
真棒
Cheers.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
海斯博士派我连夜赶来的
Dr. Hess sent me on the overnight.
想帮你把手
Thought you could use an extra set of hands.
也就是说  你是她的走狗
Oh, to put it another way, you're her lapdog.
来看着我的
Here to keep an eye on me.
我是来帮忙的
I'm here to help.
你想帮忙
You want to help?
别干扰我
Stay out of my way.
那恐怕不行
I'm afraid that's not an option.
抱歉  我们今天关门了
Sorry, we're closed for the day.
那是你的病人病例吗
Those your patient files?
我病人的病例跟你无关
My patient history is none of your business.
这是我的语音信箱  请留你的语音邮件
This is my voicemail. Make your voice a mail.
拜托  小卡  我给你打过三通电话了
Come on, Cass. I've called you three times now.
能不能回电话
Will you call me back?
我们查到大衮的线索了
We've got a line on Dagon.
我们需要你帮忙
We need your help.
你查过了那晚那间爱达荷州仓库被烧前
So you ran the plates of every car that drove past
所有经过了它的车的车牌
that warehouse in Idaho just before it burned down?
是的  大部分车是本地的  但有一辆不是
Yeah. Most of them were local, but one wasn't.
查到注册在一个德米特·考普名下
It came up registered to Dermott Culp.
怎么
So...
而他一年前失踪了
So he went missing a year ago.
好吧
Okay.
我追踪了他的车  在爱荷华州
I tracked his car to Iowa.
看到他从一栋建筑里出来
Found him coming out of a building
还扛着一具尸体
carrying a dead body.
德米特是个杀手喽
So Dermott's a killer?
德米特是个恶魔
Dermott's a demon.
猎人
Hunter.
恶魔
Demon.
克劳力的人吗
Uh, one of Crowley's?
为大衮工作
Works for Dagon.
替她掩盖踪迹
Covers her tracks.
(凯莉·克莱恩)
(删除)
明智
Smart.
哥们  别夸坏人
Dude, don't compliment the bad guys.
你知道凯莉现在在哪吗
So do you know where Kelly is now?
不  但德米特
No, but before Dermott got
被刺中心脏之前
stabbed in the heart...
漂亮
Nice.
他给了我她的手机号
He gave me her phone number.
嗯  很棒
Yeah, nice.
我还算忠诚的子民
My loyal...ish subjects,
如今世道艰险
these troubled times,
我知道你们可能不确定
I'm aware there might be some confusion
该向谁效忠
as to where you're supposed to place your loyalty.
就算路西法被关回了笼子
Even with Lucifer back in the Cage,
还有些人想帮助他
there are those of you who would try to help him...
因为他让你们害怕
because he scares you
或让你们贪婪
or engorges you.
光是路西法能回归的可能
Just the chance that Lucifer could come back,
传言  都足以让你们中一些人
the rumor, would've been enough to keep some of you
密谋反对我  给我搞破坏
working against me, undermining me,
给我找麻烦
being a royal pain in my...
让我蛋疼
pert, royal ass.
但瞧啊  野兽已被驯服
But lo, the beast has been humbled.
他将亲口说出
From his own lips, you will hear proclaimed
地狱唯一真正的统治者
the one, true leader of all Hell.
瞧
See...
我并不仅仅击败了魔鬼
I didn't just beat the Devil.
我还驯服了他
I tamed him.
这完全是出于你的自由意志吧
This is all done of your own free will, is it not?
是的  王上
Yes, my Lord.
瞧啊  孩子们
Look, kids.
我叫他去哪他就去哪  我叫他做啥他就做啥
He goes where I tell him. He does what I tell him.
他是我的狗狗
He is my dog.
该表演了  马默杜克
Showtime, Marmaduke.
是  王上
Yes, my Lord.
他说得对  朋友们
He's right, my friends.
地狱只有一个真正的统治者
There is only one true ruler of Hell.
就是我
Me.
-就是我  是吧  -是的
- And that is me, is it not? - Oh, yes.
而你诚心地
And you surrender your
支持这唯一的真正统治者  对吗
heartfelt support to that one true ruler?
绝对的
Absolutely.
那么你要对那些
And what do you have to say to those
还不确定该服从谁的人说什么
who are still unsure of whom they must obey?
我要说
I say this --
不支持这位唯一真王的人
anyone who does not support this one true king,
一定会遭受无法忍受的
can be assured of suffering unendurable
永恒痛苦
and everlasting agony.
怎么听不到掌声
I don't hear applause.
特纳医生说的很明确  我需要锌和铁
Dr. Turner was very specific. I need zinc and iron.
嗯  知道了
Yeah, got it.
这篇文章上还提到了钙
And this article says calcium.
好  再见
Cool. Bye.
克莱恩小姐
Ms. Kline.
喂
‭Yes?
我是特纳医生办公室的奥利弗
This is Oliver in Dr. Turner's office.
他今天希望您来趟办公室
He'd like to see you in the office today.
我刚去过  他说一切都好的
I, uh, I was just in there. He said everything was fine.
嗯  他又看了一下您的检测结果
All right, well, he looked back through your test results
想跟您说些事
and there are some things he'd like to discuss.
下午5点您方便吗
Does 5:00 p.m. work for you?
我恐怕走不开
I-I-I don't think I can get away.
他说这真的很重要
Well, he said it's very important.
-5点行吗  -好吧
- 5:00 p.m.? - ‭Um...sure.
那好  到时见
Good, see you then.
厉害
Cool. ‭
我以为你会一个人来呢
I thought you'd be coming alone.
我以为我们已经彼此信任了呢
Well, I thought we'd gotten past our trust issues.
如果大衮出现
Look, if Dagon shows,
我们会需要一切帮助
we're gonna need all the help we can get.
兰尼·罗林斯
Renny Rawlings.
新来的
New man.
好吧
Right.
我是萨姆  这位是艾琳·莱希
I'm Sam. This is Eileen Leahy.
女妖姑娘
Ah, the banshee girl.
我们有你的档案
We have a file.
据米克告诉我
From what Mick tells me,
你们都没接受过正规训练
neither of you have any formal training.
真有趣
Fascinating.
-我在肯德里克斯时是班级状元  -没人在乎
- I was top of my class at Kendricks -- - No one cares.
我照你要求的拿来了柯尔特枪
I, uh, brought the Colt just like you asked.
但必须还回总部
But it's gotta go back to HQ.
米克  我们不是已经信任彼此了吗
Gee, Mick, I thought we'd gotten past the trust issues.
(西看医疗诊所)
冷静点  跟我走
‭Stay cool. Walk with me.
迪恩
Dean?
就这些人了
This everyone?
嗯  小卡还没有消息
Yeah. Still no word from Cass.
好吧  真好
Right. Great.
这是谁
Who's this?
-他跟米克来的  -我是兰尼·罗林斯
- He's with Mick. - I'm Renny Rawlings.
-肯德里克斯毕业  -好啊  不在乎
- Graduated Kendricks top of my -- - Right. I don't care.
来吧
‭Come on.
-别  -好吧
- Don't. - ‭Okay.
凯莉
Kelly...
听着  我们都知道
Listen, we -- we all know
你的处境很...
you're in a really...
难做  我们只是想
difficult situation, and we -- we just...
我们想帮忙
We wanna help.
你管这叫帮忙
You call this helping?
听着  凯莉  那孩子  它不能...
Look, Kelly... That kid, it's... I mean, it can't...
那是路西法的孩子
I mean, it's Lucifer's.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你觉得我希望这样的吗
You think I wanted this to happen?
他利用了我
He used me.
但我爱这个孩子
But I love this child.
你将对那个孩子毫无意义
You will mean absolutely nothing to that child.
那孩子将杀死我们所有人
That child will kill us all.
不会那样的  我们...
That's -- that's not happening, okay? We're...
我们会有办法的
we're gonna figure something out. We will. We --
-这太荒唐了  -别
- This is absurd. - Don't.
她来了
She's here.
我不是有意的
I didn't... I didn't mean to.
我打的是那个恶魔
I was shooting at the demon.
-我...  -不  等等
- I'm -- - ‭No, no, wait up.
那是个意外
It was an accident.
没事的
It's all right.
你干什么
What are you doing?
她杀了个记录者
She killed a Man of Letters.
她必须死
S-she has to die.
-那是个意外  -无所谓
- It was an accident! - It doesn't matter!
要守准则
The Code.
不  去他的准则
No, hey, screw the Code.
别让我更难做了
Don't make this harder than it already is.
米克  你不用这样的
Mick, you don't have to do this.
我必须这么做
Yes, I do!
求你
Please.
别
Don't.
求你  别
Please. Please don't.
但准则另有要求
The Code demands otherwise.
求你  求你
Please. Please! ‭
米克  听我说
Mick, Mick, listen to me.
米克  我知道你们有
Mick, look, I-I know you guys h-have this
必须盲目遵守的记录者准则
Men of Letters Code you blindly answer to, but...
但听着  你不非得那么做的  米克
look, you don't have to do that, Mick.
你比那强
You're better than that.
你只需要听自己的
You only have to answer to yourself.
你只需要做你认为正确的事
You only have to do what you know is right.
你只需要遵从自己的准则
You only have to answer to your own code.
走吧
Just go.
嗯
Yeah.
真是没料到
Well, that was unexpected.
但令人振奋
But invigorating.
我得说  我最初遇到你时  没料到会这样
I must say, when I first met you, I didn't see this coming.
我当时想的是
My thought at the time was,
我最终得杀了她
"I'll end up shooting this one"
生活处处是惊喜
Life is full of surprises.
凯奇
Ketch.
怎么
Yes?
你不会想太多吧
You're not...reading anything into this.
比如
Like?
Like...
这有任何意义
it means anything.
当然...
It...
你不必担心
You really needn't worry. I...
事实上  我没...
Truth is, I'm not...
那个心
built for that.
我猜你也没有
And I suspect you aren't either.
我有
You're wrong.
但那是很久以前了
But that was a long time ago.
那我们没事了吧
So we're good?
是啊
We are.
我注意到你接受我的建议了
And I notice you took my advice.
建议
Advice?
你要做出选择  工作  还是家庭关系
You had a choice to make -- your work or family ties.
知道吗
You know what?
这并不是非此即彼的
It's not either/or.
我跟我儿子也经历了这样的谈话
I have the same discussion with my boys.
我并不是选了猎魔不选他们
I'm not choosing hunting over them.
为什么非得是选一个放弃一个
Why does it have to be one or the other?
你想要一切吗
So you want to have it all?
我在努力
Tryin' to.
那祝贺你
Good for you.
情况如何
So how we lookin'?
你确定克劳力在别处忙吗
You're sure Crowley is occupied elsewhere?
他在巡视呢
Yeah, he's on his rounds.
克劳力还要享受两个半小时
Crowley's got, like, two and a half more hours
被人拍马屁
of gettin' his pert, royal ass kissed.
左上象限没问题
Well, upper left quadrant is sound.
恢复状况良好  没发现增生
Restoration's holding. No laminations detected.
左下方也是
Lower left, likewise.
你的决定是正确的
You made the right decision, you know.
等尘埃落定
'Cause when the dust settles,
我们中只会剩下一个人
there's only gonna be one of us standing...
而且不会是那个操着一口外国口音的
and it ain't gonna be the guy with the accent,
懂吗
if you know what I mean.
我很感动
I'm very, very impressed.
您会很高兴知道
You'll be happy to know the...
皮囊完全没问题
the vessel is completely sound.
修复得很好
The repairs are secure.
安保系统呢
And the security system?
允许克劳力把我变成他的手偶的
Whatever it is that lets Crowley turn me into his own
不管是什么魔法
personal sock puppet.
怎么不说话
I don't hear words.
那个系统还完好无损
The -- the s-system is very much I-intact.
你可以解除它吧
But you can disarm it?
我并不是个有耐心的人
I'm not really known for my patience.
-我没办法  -谁有
- I don't quite have the means -- - Who does?
-斯皮瓦克  是他设计了  -他在哪
- ‭Spivak. He designed -- - Where is he?
死了
Dead.
Dead?
对
Dead.
那个系统安装好后
Uh, yeah, after the system was installed,
克劳力就杀了斯皮瓦克  以保密
Crowley killed Spivak to safeguard its secrets.
好吧
Well...
你可以破解的吧
You can crack it, right?
嗯  我需要点时间
Y-yeah. I just need some time.
我会尽快的
I'll -- I'll be quick.
很好
Good.
因为我要闷疯了
'Cause I am gettin' stir crazy.
而且我要当爹了
And I'm about to be a dad.
你没事吧
You okay?
有事
No.
他不是个怪物
He wasn't a monster.
他是
He was...
我
I...
那是个无心之失
It was a mistake.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
少来
Oh, don't even.
我试过了  但你显然不可信任
I tried, but clearly, you can't be trusted.
我只是担心宝宝
I was worried about the baby.
我是想保护他
I'm trying to protect him.
亲爱的  你做不到
Oh, honey. You can't.
你不需要
I mean, you don't need to.
我没骗你
I wasn't lying.
你的宝宝非常强大
Your baby's strong, so strong.
不管发生什么  他都不会有事
Whatever happens, he is going to be just fine.
但你
But you...
就有事了
won't.
嗯  那怪怪的疼痛感
Yeah, those weird little pains?
后面还会更糟
Just a taste of what's to come.
因为  生一个拿非利人
'Cause, you know, birthing a nephilim?
是致命的
Fatal.
一直都是
Always.
凯奇
Ketch.
你为什么叫我来
Why'd you call me here?
不是我
Oh, I didn't.
戴维斯先生
Mr. Davies.
海斯博士
Dr. Hess.
我不知道你离开了伦敦
I didn't think you left London.
我也不想
I don't.
但我受命于
But I have been tasked
其他长老
by the other elders to
来挽救这急转直下的局面
fix this rapidly deteriorating situation.
-夫人  拜托  我...  -你是否想说
- Ma'am, please. I'm -- - Are you about to tell me
你已经尽力了
that you are doing the best that you can?
两天前
Two days ago,
据你的报告称
according to your own report,
你让一个地狱王子
you let a Prince of Hell escape
还有路西法孩子的母亲逃走了
and the mother of Lucifer's child.
而我最得力的一个手下被一名美国猎人杀了
And one of my best men was murdered by an American Hunter,
-而你没有处决她  -容我说一句
- whom you allowed to live. - If I might --
这些猎人已经失控了
These Hunters are out of control.
尤其是温家兄弟
The brothers Winchester, in particular,
而贝维尔夫人早已竭力阐明
which Lady Bevell has exhaustedly documented.
夫人  请您听我说
Ma'am, if -- if you could just listen --
听什么  更多借口吗
To what? More excuses?
不
No.
我不想听
I don't think I will.
猎人就是狗  戴维斯先生
Hunters are dogs, Mr. Davies.
你给他们下令  他们遵守
You give them an order, and they obey.
这才是正道
That's how it works.
告诉我  是这样吗
So tell me, do they?
他们遵你的命吗
Do they obey you?
不
No.
当然不了
Of course not.
所以
So...
找到这个艾琳·莱希  杀了她
this Eileen Leahy will be found and killed
这是准则的要求
in accordance with the Code.
至于温家人
As for the Winchesters,
如同对待所有叛逆猎人  调查他们
like any rebellious Hunter, they will be investigated.
如果被判有罪  就处决
And, if found guilty, executed.
"如果"
"If"?
如果被判有罪
If they're found guilty?
猎人难道不总是被判有罪吗
Aren't Hunters always found guilty?
小心点  戴维斯先生
Be careful, Mr. Davies.
不
No.
我跟随了记录者一辈子
My entire life with the Men of Letters,
从未坏过规矩
I never broke a rule.
是的
And yes,
起初  萨姆和迪恩的行事方式令我震惊
at first I was shocked at how Sam and Dean operate.
但贝维尔夫人没有提到的
But what Lady Bevell doesn't mention
是他们挽救的生命
is the lives they've saved,
杀掉的怪物
monsters destroyed,
以及得到的更好的结果  那不是因为准则
and outcomes made better not because of the Code,
而是因为萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
but because of Sam and Dean Winchester's
知道什么是对的
sense of what's right.
这才是问题的关键
And that is the crux of the matter.
准则不是建议
The Code is not a suggestion.
是绝对的要求
It's an absolute.
准则将我们和怪物区分开
The Code is what separates us from the monsters.
是我们遵守的秩序
It is the order by which we all live.
不
No.
准则是用来逼小孩子
The code is what makes a young boy
杀挚友的
kill his best friend.
我小时候一无所有
When I was a child, I had nothing.
我欠你一切  所以我服从了
I owed you everything, and I obeyed.
但我现在是大人了  海斯博士
But I'm a man now, Dr. Hess,
我看得到选择了
and I can see the choices,
我选择做正确的事
and I choose to do the right thing.
早
Mornin'.
你
Hey, you,
有小卡的消息了吗
you hear anything from Cass yet?
没有  还失踪着
No. Still MIA.
你觉得他还好吧
You think he's all right?
我不知道
I don't know.
艾琳呢
Where's Eileen?
她走了
She took off.
说要回爱尔兰待一阵
Uh, said she's heading back to Ireland for a while.
需要点时间吧
Just needs some time, I guess.
我能理解
Yeah, I get that.
欢迎回来  亲爱的
Welcome back, sweetheart.
结束了
It's over.
收服美国猎人的大实验
The grand experiment recruiting American Hunters
彻底失败了
has failed. Utterly.
要我怎么做
What would you like me to do?
铲除他们
Exterminate them.
一个不剩
Every...last...one.
(机密文件)